[siren sound]
[♪ Interesting music]
[Symbol] Fish oil, really, seed
People really, Mr.
Isn't that too much? uh?
[So Ryong] Something
Doesn’t it smell like intentional negligence?
Oh, it's completely intentional.
I even saw the blood
[Limit] That’s not it.
[Symbol] Ah, use the fire extinguisher now.
Destroy the entire office now
The face is now...
I made it to this point
This, this now
It's not intentional, is it intentional?
That's intentional
[Limit] It’s intentional.
- [Symbol] Yes?
- [Limit’s Sigh]
[Sound of running footsteps]
- [Car starting sound]
- [Sound of car door closing]
- [Staff] Reporter Hwang
- [Reporter Hwang] Yes
- [Employee] Get in quickly, there’s no time.
- [Reporter Hwang] Yes, yes
[Sound of car door closing]
[Daeyong] Oh my
The sprinkler didn't work
Thank you, thank you
Look, the entire coverage is wet.
Wow, it's terrible
[So-ryong] What happened over there?
- [Daeyong] A seven-year-old child went missing.
- [Mobile phone alarm sound]
in their apartment
It's too late to report to the child's mother.
When was the Amber Alert issued?
I heard it’s already been over three hours
[Symbol] Ah, look at this.
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Reporters’ urgent voices]
[Reporter] Hey, did you find it?
- [Camera shutter sound]
- [Noisy noises from reporters]
[Chuckling sound]
[shrug]
[Doorbell sounds]
[Knocking sound]
[Detective 1] Are you there?
-Are you there?
- [doorbell sound]
[Detective 1’s surprised voice]
What are you doing here at this time of night?
[Detective 1] Oh, yes, I’m a police officer.
I'm looking for a seven year old boy
Please cooperate
Yes, my child is in middle school.
- Annoying, really.
- [Detective 1] Child
[Woman] Huh?
What are you doing now?
[Detective 1] Are those shoes your son’s?
[♪ dark music]
[Woman] What is that?
- [Embarrassed sound]
- [Detective 1] Where is the kid? yes?
- No, I don't know what you mean.
- [Detective 1] Where is the kid?
- [Woman] Let’s go, let’s go
- [Detective 1] Hey, go in!
[Detective 2] It looks like the door is locked.
- [Woman's heavy breathing]
- [Clicking sound]
[Detective 1] Open this door
[Woman] What about our Junyoung’s room?
My husband and I don’t go in without permission either.
No, these days already
It’s really during the Olympiad…
[Detective 1] Come on, hurry!
Do you know your intermittent sleep schedule?
Hey, you can't wake me up.
[Detective 1] Mr. Ai, come out.
- [Junyoung’s mother] What is it? Why, why, why?
- [Detective 1] IC
Oh, really! How much is this door?
You must be really crazy, Mr.
- [Junyoung’s heavy breathing]
- [Door lock operating sound]
[Junyoung’s mother] Is it Mingeun or something, huh?
Just try not to exist, Mr. Wow.
[♪ Nervous music]
[Junyoung mocks laughter]
What is this, what is this?
[Junyoung’s mock sigh] My father
Because I’m a professor at a veterinary school.
I brought it from the lab.
[Junyoung mocks laughter]
Oh, my kid is going to be a doctor.
[Sniffing sniffing sound]
Oh my son
Son, wake up for a moment.
son
- [Tense sound effect]
- [Detective 1] Hey, Mr.
[Junyoung mocks surprised sound]
[Snoring sound]
[Cat crying]
[Old man coughing]
[Heavy breathing]
- [Old man’s surprised gasp]
- [♪ Dark Music]
[light sigh]
[popping sound]
- [Old man’s surprised voice]
- [Tense sound effect]
What are you so surprised about?
Grandfather told you to do it.
[shaking breathing]
[Junyoung] I also kill the cats in this neighborhood
Kill that kid and bring it back.
[Crying] Otherwise, I’ll rape you again.
I'm going to kill my mom and dad too.
That's right, grandpa
- Meow
- [Cat crying]
- [Junyoung’s crying]
- Go quickly, go to the temple, go quickly!
[Old man] This guy!
Get out of here now!
[♪ Music that heightens tension]
[Junyoung’s laughter]
[Old man's urgent voice]
[Cat's sharp cry]
[Sound of cutting]
It's warm
[laughter]
[Employee] Criminals who threw smoke bombs
I just embroidered
I just obeyed the voice of the Lord
I'm just insisting hard
Yes, and
Cyber terrorism caused by Dr. Trigger
The president of our company
They say they handle it through the legal team.
police, media
He told me not to make any contact.
Especially PD Oh So-ryong.
You, Mr. Lee
After acting out useless nonsense
It's just, man, out.
[Daeyong] Oh, that's a bit...
[Employee laughing] No, no.
no, not me
- It's not me, it's the boss.
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
Tell it like this
Do it and give it to me
As always
Don't worry, I'll do it very gently.
Please tell me it's poetry
[Daeyong is fed up]
[So-ryong] Yes, Detective Yu.
[Detective Yoo] PD Oh
Where is that piss-poor PD now?
Can you confirm the location?
PD Han?
[So-ryong] Why PD Han?
Could it be that the PD
The kid who made a false report
Do you have any information?
If it's the kid who reported it...
[Detective Yu] That’s the house I went to yesterday.
Oh, this is an embargo.
- Did you hear about the missing child case?
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[Limit] Now
[Emphasized sound effect]
- [So-Ryong] Kang Ki-ho, take your camera.
- [Sound of door closing]
One PD took CCTV photos from a convenience store
Let's go by car first.
[Symbol] Oh, where are you going all of a sudden?
[So-ryong] Let’s talk as we go, we don’t have time.
[Siho] Ah, bro, what are you doing?
Come quickly
[So-ryong] That missing child
I think he died
The police said they found signs of a murder.
- [Symbol] Yes?
- [So Ryong] The important thing is
The suspect who killed that child
Son Jun-young is a middle school student.
I'm not even fourteen yet
[Team Member] Baby, baby
Are you saying he killed it?
Ah, then now
Are you going to follow that guy?
[Hando] This is the road to that house.
That's right, Grandpa Yoon Nam-gi went during the day.
[So-ryong] I’m going to that house now.
-Why are you there…
- [Soryong’s Sigh]
According to the detective
They say Son Jun-young’s location is listed there.
No way now
Is that Son Jun-young? No, right?
Let's go, for now
- [Siren sound]
- [Fire truck horn]
[Symbol] I think there was a fire?
[So-ryong] Oh, I can’t do that.
Captain, as quickly as possible.
- [♪ Nervous music]
- [Noisy noise]
- [Detective Yoo’s busy speaking voice]
- [Hando’s urgent breathing]
We're PD, not police.
It's a real situation now
That bastard is in there
What if I stay with my grandfather?
So I have to wait longer
They do it as quickly as possible
Be rescued safely
[So-ryong] Detective Yu!
[Detective Yoo] Oh
Hey! Oh, let me in, let me in
[Soryong] Is that right?
[Junyoung’s cough]
- [♪ Dark Music]
- [Junyoung] Please save me!
[Crew 1] Rescue victim found!
[Crew 2] Rescue victim found!
- Student, are you okay?
- [Junyoung’s labored breathing]
Can you walk?
[Junyoung’s cough]
[Operator 3] Are you okay?
[Junyoung’s labored breathing]
[Crew 4] Rescue target
We will transport you!
- [Operator 5] Transfer!
- [Ambulance starting sound]
- [Siren sound]
- [Sound of people talking]
[Hando’s urgent breathing]
- [The urgent sounds of the crew]
- [Woman] Oh my, what is that person?
[Symbol] Brother, brother, Han Do-hyung!
[Hando’s surprised gasp]
[Operator 6] Executing first aid measures
I will transfer you to Sunwon University Hospital.
[Rough breathing]
[Left] People who live in society
I have to be neat
- [♪ Dark Music]
- You came, so that's fine.
[Rough breathing]
[Heavy sound effect]
[shaking breathing]
[Detective Yu] Now
What are you doing now? Control it!
[Detective] Step back, step back!
- [Detective Yu] Hey, control it!
- [Detective] Get back!
[siren sound]
Is that you?
[Limit] Who, who…
I wasn't the one to hurt you
That grandfather
[Hando’s trembling breathing]
I
I told you so
I need to catch that bastard
I told you!
- [Symbol] Brother, why are you like this, why, why…
- [Limit] Me!
So cruel to cats
The bastard who killed
people
Are you saying you can’t kill people?
I told you, I did!
[sigh]
[Rough breathing]
[Beeping sound]
[Heart beating sound effect]
[Sounds around become quiet]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Heavy breathing]
[♪ Calm music]
[Hando’s labored breathing]
- [Tap sound]
- [Meaningful sound effects]
[Rough breathing]
[groan]
[So-ryong] One PD!
[Symbol] Han, Handa hyung!
Han Do, come to your senses.
[So-ryong] Here, someone here...
[Sign, Soryong’s distant words]
[camera shutter sound]
[Heavy sound effect]
[busy sound]
[Mumbling] Die, Mr. Lee.
[Limit] Die
[Soryong] His condition is zero…
[Doctor] It’s because of the sedative.
I feel relaxed
It will feel good
There is nothing wrong with the test results.
You're healthier than me
No, why does someone like that fall down?
Well, temporarily
You were greatly shocked or
[Doctor] I couldn’t control my anger and suddenly
It may have been out of focus.
For now, in this state
Let's wait an hour or two and see.
[Doctor yawns]
Hey, in the office
While drawing the line fearfully
[Symbol] Oh, what
Is he your biological grandfather or what?
Take care, don't let an accident happen.
[Symbol] Oh, where are you going?
What is this? Investigation without detention?
Oh, on what basis?
There is no risk of escape for minors.
You need peace of mind and body.
Do you understand?
Oh, then what, above
Would you like to go directly to Son Jun-young now?
There is an order to everything
Solid evidence comes first
[Reporters muttering]
- [Reporter Hwang] Oh PD!
- [Reporter] Triggers are always given preferential treatment.
Oh, really
[Reporter Hwang] Oh, oh PD!
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Child [urgent sound]
[Reporter Hwang] PD!
Oh PD, Oh PD, Oh PD
Oh, wait a minute.
I…
- What are your lips? for a moment…
- [So-ryong] It’s okay, it’s okay
What's this story that hasn't been said before?
There's something there, really?
[Soryong] Jinwoo, I’m sorry…
no, no
We are part of the same company.
to me now
Talk to me, it's okay.
[Soryong sighs] I’m really sorry.
I can't tell you anything
No, honey, now…
It's me, I'm your boyfriend
Are work and love the same?
[Jinwoo] Oh So-ryong, huh?
You were such a stuck-up person.
Soryong, you?
[So-ryong] Me now
I have something really urgent to do
Jinwoo, let’s talk later.
[Jinwoo] What the hell am I
What kind of existence is it to you?
Xiaoryong, wait a minute, huh? Wait a minute
Bar, no ring, no ring
You don't have a ring?
I don't have a ring
Xiaoryong, I don’t have a ring.
Huh? There is no ring...
[after exhaling]
[Snoring sound]
[Hando’s surprised gasp]
[Hando's irritated breathing]
[Nurse 1] Teacher Joo
Did you see the Son Jun-young news?
He's so rich
[Nurse 2] What do you do if you’re rich?
I was threatened with rape by my grandfather.
Even killing a child
Is that because you told me to do that? It's me
[Nurse 1] Plus, the grandfather
He stabbed himself with a knife and set fire to it.
He committed suicide
‘I’m a victim too’
[Nurse 2] Victim?
There are no signs of sexual assault.
A knife in the stomach?
Just by looking at it, it looks like someone stabbed me.
[Nurse 1] What’s more important than facts
Unplay…
[Sounds of surprise from nurses]
[Nurse 2] Oh, patient.
No, it just moves so suddenly
You can't do that.
This is PD
[Limit] Trigger
Oh my
[Laughing] Oh, wow, my goodness.
Hey, should I actually report this or not?
I was really thinking about it.
- Um, maybe...
- [♪ Heavy music]
- [Mingeun’s mother] Our Mingeun’s eyes
- [Police officers’ embarrassing sounds]
What happened to my eyes?
I'll just ask that and leave.
Please!
[Min Geun Bu] Who would do it?
Who is the victim?
Why are you protecting that devilish guy?
[Mingeun’s name] You have Mingeun’s eyes
How did you do it!
- [Min Geun Mo’s struggling sounds]
- [Min Geun’s father’s lamenting voice]
- [Police officers’ surprised sounds]
- [Min Geun Bu] Honey, honey
- [Police 1] Are you okay?
- [Min Geun’s wife] Honey, honey!
[Nurse] Are you okay? Are you okay?
[Surprising] Oh my, please take this person to the emergency room.
Please move it, right now.
[Police 1] Oh, we are now
I have to protect this place...
[Nurse] Oh, quick!
I'm going to die like this!
Because I will be guarding this place
Quickly
Ah, quickly!
- [Police 1] Oh, I understand.
- [Police 2] I will carry you.
[Mingeunbu] Are you okay? honey
[Police 1] Come to your senses.
Yes? Come to your senses
[Nurse] Go quickly, quickly.
[Police 1] Boy, I
You can't get out of here.
- [Nurse’s urging]
- [Police officers’ embarrassed sounds]
[Rough breathing]
Are you okay?
[♪ dark music]
[Sound of door closing]
Man, how did you get in?
The question is I
Why did you kill grandpa?
Why did you kill that kid?
[sigh]
[Junyoung] Should I scream?
Is there anyone?
When I turn off my cell phone
I'll teach you
[Limit] One more
Even cute cats
Why did you kill innocent lives?
uncle
Isn’t it Seoul National University?
what?
No, to get the correct answer
The question must be accurate
The thing that killed the trash old man
not me
Hey man
[Junyoung] With that bastard
What I'm saying
'Cause I heard it all
[Owner] Wow, because the trigger occurred
Now you're done with the criminal, huh?
It won't be a matter of time before you catch it.
Right? Right?
[Junyoung] Look at this
People say they feel sorry for me
Well, even if it turns over
Anyway, I won't go to jail because it's a quick law.
No one can beat me
I'm invincible
Where are you putting the trigger?
[Excited breathing]
To their mom and dad
I'll never find my eyes
Please tell me
Man, do you know what?
- [♪ Music becomes bizarre]
- out of breath
Just
[laughter]
When it's about to break
Yuri Gagarin
Even when I saw the Earth from space
Is that exactly what it felt like?
Ha, her eyes were really pretty.
Ah
Don't you know Yuri Gagarin?
[Junyoung speaks in English]
[♪ Soaring music]
- Hmm?
- [♪ Dark Music]
[urgent knocking sound]
[Detective's irritated speech]
[The nurse is surprised] PD, PD!
[Junyoung] I guess the police are here
Man, are you screwed now?
[laughter]
[limited laughter]
[Exclamation mixed with laughter]
Ah, I should have gone to ‘Exciting Animal Heaven’, hehe.
Why did I fall into something like this?
I didn't get an answer
It was here, answer
[Limit] Hey
What do you think your future is?
Youngest serial killer?
[laughter]
Or a rare devil?
My goal is to kill 100 people.
[Laughing] What did you say?
We are bastards like you
Don't call me 'devil' or 'murderer' like that.
just
- Loser
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[Limit] You are just an end game loser
There's no hope
How to touch?
That only works in law
There's nothing like that on this floor
Human rights?
Hmm, nothing more like that.
Oh, just one thing
Young Go Jjal
Have you heard of it?
Broadcasting stations only increase viewership ratings, right?
No matter whose life becomes shit
I don't care if it's soybean paste
Take them one by one
Take it all out
[laughter]
What, what do you say?
Don't you understand this kid with an IQ of 180?
[Limit] This is why
I need to improve my EQ
Hey, End Game Loser, listen up.
What is Younggo Jjal?
‘By stuffing your sins with a camera’
‘From this time on, I will love you forever.
'Stuffed with pictures of suffering'
This means
[Hando speaks in English]
- [Junyoung’s urgent breathing]
- [Mobile phone operation sound]
What is it?
the camera
Is it only on your phone?
-You can’t go to Seoul National University either.
- [Junyoung’s trembling breathing]
[Junyoung’s swearing sound]
[Each person’s surprised voice]
[Limit] Oh, what is it?
I came in thinking it was our hospital room.
The kids were surprised and I was surprised too.
No, the police did this
What if I don't do my job?
You have to keep it straight!
Just file a complaint, really.
- I'm leaving the hospital.
- [Nurse] Oh, yeah, yeah
[Detective] Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, hey
Hey, wait a minute!
[Detective] Wait, wait, wait
- Wait a minute.
- [Hando’s moans]
[The sound of both of them breathing heavily]
You are Trigger PD, right?
Be sure to broadcast
[Limit] Yes?
Trigger doesn't broadcast
Because I’m going to ask for all your sins today
[Detective] Come to your senses
Fighting
[Heavy breathing]
- [Heavy breathing]
- [Sound of door opening and closing]
- [Sound of door opening]
- [Woman] Yes, mother.
- [Sound of door closing]
- No, according to our lawyer.
That old man died
It's a godsend
[urgent breathing]
Of course, they ordered it all, right?
- [Tang]
- [Hando’s surprised gasp]
No, wait a minute.
yes
yes, mother
- [Sound of door closing]
- [Sigh]
[Rough breathing]
[♪ Interesting and heavy music]
[Junyoung’s swearing sound]
[sigh]
[Limit] small, small
How do you catch all of this?
[sigh]
[crow crying]
[Leaving] Is this a camera?
[Laughing] Yes, inside
A very small camera
There's one in it
It seems odd, right?
Ah, the technology is good.
[So-ryong and Namgi’s faint smile]
[So-ryong] When the teacher is not there
people sneaking in and out
Now everything will be filmed here.
That bad guy who took the cat
Let's see if it comes again
This is
You know it’s a secret between us, right?
The kid who peed will love it
yes?
Gungye
I look at people carefully
[Soryong’s Lament]
[Detective Yoo] I thought it was an ally
[Soryong’s sigh]
This isn't between us, right?
Hey, youngest child, go to the back.
[Detective] Yes, I understand.
[So-ryong] Oh, take it all
It doesn't even turn on
oh, look
[Detective Yu] Huh? Is this really going to happen?
This should interfere with the execution of official duties.
plus concealing evidence
before it is evidence
This is our broadcasting station’s private property.
Since it is a public broadcaster, is it public property?
[disapproving sound]
Leave it to me where I decide
How about watching it together?
Is that one condition?
- No, well, it's both a business and a business.
- [♪ Interesting music]
One immigration record
Thank you if you recognize me
[Man] Oh, this is
Better than what I heard on the phone
- The extent of this damage is
- [Grunting sound]
Wow, it's much bigger.
Can't you?
[Detective Yoo] That’s right
Let’s leave it to the National Forensic Service, kid.
Our technology is good these days.
If I can't do it
It doesn't appear anywhere in Korea.
Now, which way is the result of this?
I take it for granted
Why are you frowning like this?
[Detective Yoo] Uh-huh, really.
I came this far as I said.
Are you going to keep doing this?
Ah, magnesium these days.
It's because it's not enough
Sounds like magnesium
Then the immigration record...
Is it sewage?
[Detective Yoo] When the results come out
You should do it while looking at the contents.
[Call connection tone]
- [Call end sound]
- [Sigh of symbol]
[Symbol] Where did you go?
I really
This time I won't leave you alone
No, why is it like this?
I can't make a phone call, really?
Ah, if you go, you will go, if you come, you will come.
You need to tell me
Do you know how much I found?
‘We Need Teamwork, Understand’?
You're not listening to me again, are you?
Wow, pee teamwork, those guys.
[Lawyer 1] I am suffering damage.
I can't sit idly by anymore...
[Sound of mouth opening]
[Attorney 2] Yes, there is no problem.
Okay [clears cough]
Even though the investigation is ongoing
[Lawyer] The investigation
Even in ongoing situations
Due to indiscriminate personal information stealing and malicious comments,
Our client, a minor,
We are suffering enormous damage.
I decided I couldn't sit by and watch anymore.
As of this time
related to the incident
Speculative reporting or fake news
To the perpetrator who writes malicious comments
decided to take legal action
I decided
That's it.
[Reporter 1] Hey, I have a question!
[Attorney] I’m sorry, but
I will not be taking any questions today.
[Limit] Then don’t ask questions
Do you get the facts?
- [Reporters chattering]
- [♪ Nervous music]
cat serial murder case
To the broadcasting station PD who is covering the story
Son Jun-young intentionally
Are you aware that you made a false report?
- [Reporters muttering]
- [Camera shutter sound]
[Attorney] I’ll say it again,
Unconfirmed speculative remarks or…
one more
[Limit] Son Jun-young
Sexual harassment and murder instructions
They are claiming that they are receiving it.
a few days before the crime
Mr. Son even dressed up as a woman.
I stabbed the old man with a weapon.
There is also a fact that I was joking
Did you know?
- [Reporter 2] What do you mean, this?
- [Noisy]
[Reporter 3] Is it true?
press conference today
I'll stop here
- [Attorney] Thank you
- No, I still have something to say...
[Reporters’ questions]
[Kiho’s awkward laughter]
- [Symbol] Yes, that…
- [Reporters become quiet]
Yes, I…
Since I joined the company
It's only been a week
sorry
[Reporters’ questions]
[So-ryong] What are we going to do now?
[Limit] That bastard
You killed them all, right?
You must be punished, then!
[So-ryong] That child’s
Half of the time my head doesn't turn.
- Lee Parachute
- [Hando’s absurd breathing sound]
What do you think will end this case?
The truth is revealed
He gets the punishment he deserves
Do you think you'll say 'I reflect'?
no
Of course not
That's why it's like this
[Exasperated gasp] What you just did
If it was a brain official for pressure
defamation
Even if it was a real fact
Defamation of character by timely facts
While you're being called to court
While I spend money and time and write a final letter,
He sits in a corner of a rich house
We'll giggle and play games
Ah, Mr.
I think it's because of me
the grandfather
[sigh]
If I hadn't come looking for it...
Then what
Are you alive?
[So Ryong] The stupidest thing in the world
What has already happened
I'm adding 'if'
The incident has already happened
The main character is not you
Two sad victims.
Pathetic male lead cosplay banned
no tears
You should just shut up and do your PD work.
What if it's broadcast?
That bastard really
Is arrest possible?
That fucking law
How do we change it?
your faith
They're looking for me now
There has to be something to believe in
It's natural to believe
Hope is originally invisible to the eye
No matter how hard I search outside, I can't find it
[Tap sound]
[Siho’s breathing sound]
[Siho] Producer Han took the poop.
Why are you leaving me alone?
If you want to see what faith is, follow me
I'll show you
[Man] Okay, first of all
- If you deliver bad news first,
- [Keyboard operation sound]
I couldn't get the sound
But my skills are unrivaled.
Fortunately, the part where the crime was filmed was
I saved it
- Yes
- [Soryong’s sigh of relief]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Junyoung’s heavy breathing]
- [♪ Dark and gloomy music]
- [Namgi’s labored breathing]
- [Junyoung’s sound of strength]
- [Sound of being stabbed]
- [Namgi’s surprised voice]
- [Junyoung’s labored breathing]
[Junyoung’s sound of pain]
[Junyoung] Oh, it hurts badly
- [Sound of a knife being pulled out]
- [Junyoung’s heavy breathing]
Now it's self-defense
- [Junyoung’s sound of strength]
- [Namgi’s moans]
- [Junyoung’s heavy breathing]
- [Namgi’s painful sounds]
[Soryong] What are you grabbing?
- [Man] Well, that's
- [Keyboard operation sound]
It's up to you, detective.
Too small to identify
Okay, here it is.
[popping sound]
[Detective Yoo] How could this happen?
Thinking of putting the camera down
Are you done?
[So-ryong] This is what the PD always does.
[Detective Yoo] Me and Team Leader Oh
We'll talk for a while
[Symbol] Yes, team leader
Then I'll go down there too
- [Switch operation sound]
- I will wait with Captain Bae.
[Detective Yoo] When it appears on the news
It will be very noisy
Oh PD, you really played a big role.
[Soryong] Hey…
Detective Yu
During a press briefing
Leave out our story.
What is this dazzling humility?
Oh, it's not humility, it's resentment.
When the behind-the-scenes details are revealed
We'll also talk about PD Han.
Well, people who like to talk
For no reason the PD visited me
It was like this, it was like that, oh
Even if it breaks like that, I can see it
Even if it's broken, I can see it
Why is it that big?
You said it was old-fashioned.
[Sound of intake of breath]
[Soryong] Immigration record
How did it go?
To Jo Haewon
There are no records so far
Don't you have any?
[Detective Yu] Two things.
I really didn't come in
Or you changed your personal information
I also have eyes to see
It's impossible to find out any more
[Symbol] Ah, team leader
Are you here, team leader?
Me, this
[So-ryong] Whose number is it?
This is Mingeun’s father.
[Symbol] No
I was in the emergency room earlier.
As if it was fate, you came here just in time.
So I
I told him it was Trigger PD.
Immediate interview okay
So this is it
It's going to be crazy, right?
Then I and PD Han
I'm going to Mingeun's place.
[Limit] No
Well, I’m doing the interview alone…
- [Sound of car door closing]
- [♪ Interesting music]
What?
Alone... [sigh]
When I should be neutral, I go crazy
When you have to go straight, take a back step
This unbalance
How should I understand this?
- That's not it...
- [Symbol] Not ‘no’
As a team member
At least be polite
- No...
- [Symbol] Wow, I’m really angry, really?
[Soryong’s sigh]
- Okay, go, go, go.
- [Symbol] Oh, don’t go.
- [Limit] Let's go, go, let's go, go
- [Sign] Don’t go!
[Limit] Go, go
[Symbol] Thank you
- [So-ryong] Do well.
- [Car starting sound]
[Sign] Captain, let’s go.
[Symbol] You must be in no mood.
Thank you for willingly agreeing to the interview.
thank you so much
[Mingeunbu] The situation is turning
I just can't trust anyone
[Siho] It must be very difficult
The police are working hard now.
so we can help too
I'll do my best
yes, that
That person over there is PD Hando.
- [Whine and cry]
- My name is Kang Ki-ho.
[Hando's surprised voice]
Why…
- [Limit] Ah, ah…
- [Clicking sound]
[laughter]
[Screaming scared]
- Yes, P, why is PD lying down?
- [♪ Interesting music]
- [Sympathy sound]
- [Hando’s scared voice]
[Thump]
[Hando’s sound of pain]
[Mingeun Mo] Huh?
[absurd gasping sound]
[Awkward laughter]
- [Mingeun Mo] Get out, get out!
- [Symbol] Oh, mother, those bare feet!
Bare feet, oh, it hurts
Oh my, mother
Oh, uh, mom, just a moment.
mother, mother
- [Sound of pain in the sign]
- [Limit’s Sigh]
Oh, what are you doing?
No, ah, what does he do?
Why to someone I don’t even know in person?
Are you blowing a pakyu? bar…
no, really
Tell me in advance, no
They're in a living hell right now.
What is happening now, what is this?
[Siho’s incredulous breathing]
[Limit] Ah, so I
I said I wouldn't come for an interview.
[Symbol] No, it’s really this size
A person who is afraid of dogs
What? what? ‘Animal Heaven’?
Ah, it’s really ‘what the hit’
‘What the hit’!
[Limit] No
Even if you're scared, you can still like it
- A person like me...
- [Symbol] Oh, shut up!
[Siho’s embarrassed breathing]
Yo
I mean people, Mr.
Such harsh words
Do it, really, really
Now let's go back to the office
[Crying] Oh, I really am
I'm going to turn away
Our writer Hong
Oh team leader, CP Park…
Ha, messed up today
I'm screwed, I'm screwed
Are you a reporter?
why?
No, that's not a good thing.
[Limit] What is it?
[Loud gunshots and screams in the game]
[Junyoung’s mother] Son, huh?
In times like these, huh?
Calmly solving problems
It's mind control.
[Junyoung] Oh, fuck
Even if I don’t solve this, I’m going to medical school!
- Oh, fuck.
- [Junyoung’s mother] Ugh
[Gunshots and screams continue in the game]
No, but it happened overnight
Why are there so many things happening?
[Lawyer] Ah, wow.
- Mom, is there anyone else I don't know about?
- [Junyoung mocks clearing cough]
There must be something more, right?
[Junyoung’s mother] Huh?
[♪ Meaningful music]
Uh…
No, uh, no, no, no.
no, what
It's worse than this
What could there be?
He clearly said there was none.
yes
[light laughter]
[Gunshots and screams get louder]
Well, I missed the interview...
[Writer Hong] What?
Didn't you get it?
Did they turn around?
No, Han Do, Han Do.
To Mingeun’s mother
By doing a PQ like this...
[So-ryong] Pakyu?
[Symbol] No, what
Anyway, I didn't do it today.
- That's why I was kicked out barefoot...
- [Mocha] What should I do?
I received a text message from Mingeun’s father.
Just one more call
You said you would report it…
ah…
- [Sound of banging]
- [Writer Hong] In this case
To viewers
The weapon that will appeal the most is
- [Stomping]
- These are the tears of parents.
That should serve as an opening
People focus...
[Limit] That’s a pity
Instead of selling the pain of the victims
How dangerous is the perpetrator?
Are you a cruel person?
I think it's better to show it, I think
[Writer Hong] Wow
This creepy shamelessness
Are you a cow?
If you put it that way, what about grandpa?
It's unfair that he was murdered.
accused of being a perpetrator
You're being treated like a lieutenant.
[Limit] In that sense
not a victim
[rattling sound]
What if Son Jun-young is the opening?
[♪ Heavy and interesting music]
[Sign] Have you met Son Jun-young?
Uh, how?
Well, I just came to visit you.
[Symbol] Then
The thing that disappeared from the hospital earlier, wow...
[Writer Hong] Self
brave
No, that important thing
Why do it now?
[Symbol] No, what
Didn't you do it because you didn't know someone?
That's how it was filmed anyway
It's illegal so you can't broadcast it.
Right, team leader?
[Author Hong] Just like the original
Jaeyeon picked it up
If you just add the actual voice there,
It's like a charm
No problem
- [Symbol] Yes? uh?
- [Sound of door opening and closing]
[Hando] Then, I and PD Kang
I'm going to have an interview.
[Symbol] What, what, what
What, what, what interview, yes?
Well, let’s go to Mingeun’s house.
That's right, do you want to die?
[Limit] No
Son Jun-young killed someone
[♪ dark music]
I don't think this is the first time
[Hando] I was caught because of what you said earlier.
It's not even a good thing
what does it mean
Was it 4 years ago?
With my brother who is in 3rd grade of elementary school
developmentally disabled
In a house with only two five-year-old children
[Woman 1’s surprised voice]
[Woman 2] My younger brother
There was a fatal accident
[Woman 1 crying] Lamentation
I fell into the water
- [Woman 2] But that’s it
- He's not breathing, hurry...
[Woman 2] There is a rumor that it was not an accident.
I went to Mom Cafe.
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Limit] Unless it’s an accident…
- [Woman 2] My brother killed me.
- [Woman 1’s surprised gasp]
That house
This time, room 1806, building 106
- The Son Jun-young who caused the accident this time.
- [Emphasis sound]
That's my brother
[Junyoung’s mother] Aunt
Just go away
Hey, I'll take care of it here.
Madam
Go
[Tense sound effect]
[Limit] Is it a murder or an accident?
police investigation
Are you saying you didn't do it separately?
On the back of Son Jun-young’s hand and wrist
I heard there were injuries too?
Junyoung’s mother
The child is like that because of atopy.
Oh, they say they're not parents.
What can the police do?
[Symbol] To Son Jun-young
Did you really have atopy?
Since he was born
I'm pretty without a single illness.
My second son, who had a disability, was weak.
I can't even get my mother's love
[Hando’s sigh]
[Woman] Hey, you know
When it goes on air
Aren't I getting dangerous?
Anyone who worked in that house
I am the only one
[Limit] If you wish
I won't broadcast it.
[Woman] Really?
I would be so grateful if you did so.
[Symbol] What are you saying now...
[Limit] Take off the car, take off the gun
If you go on air without anything special
Son Jun-young will be out soon, right?
[Hando’s sigh]
Killing 100 people for me
I said it was my goal
- [♪ Interesting music]
- [Symbol] What do you mean?
[Limit] Am I the third one?
Fourth…
PD
Why are you looking at me?
I've never even seen your face?
[Limit] Oh, that’s right
You said you worked for a long time, right?
[Woman] Yes
[Limit] Well, then for safety’s sake
Change your name with me...
No. Can you move?
I have to immigrate.
[Symbol] Changing the face is also...
[Limit] Plastic surgery, sex, plastic surgery
Do you know anything?
[Symbol] In the building in front of us
There is one
Is your goal really to kill 100 people?
[Embarrassed breathing]
Put it on air
[surprised gasp]
[Woman] What do you have?
In broadcast
- [Limit] Thank you
- [♪ Heavy and interesting music]
[Cat crying]
[Sneeze]
- [♪ Music that stretches]
- [Cough of limit]
- [Symbol] cut, cut
- [Cat crying]
How many times do you sneeze?
Well, I told you to be patient.
Ah, so
I told you I wouldn't do it [heavy breathing]
Because of allergies
Allergy...
Hey, you're allergic.
While I was building the set and setting it on fire
The production cost was far over.
Did you talk about it or not?
[Symbol] No, well, if you use an actor
Producer Han will pay for it?
No, but the dog is scared
Also, I guess I’m not afraid of cats
yes
'Yes'?
[Limit] But the cat
I don't like it that much, I like dogs.
It's difficult
Hey, you're a difficult person.
Me, director
Just one more time, just one more time
- [Director] Go quickly, quickly.
- [Symbol] Really, okay, okay
[Hando’s painful breathing]
Don't, don't sneeze, please
don't do it
What is this smell?
- [Thumping sound]
- Child...
Captain, do you smoke on site?
Hey, turn it off when you start filming.
[Sound of falling]
[Symbol] Ahhh
It's really eventful, eventful
Okay, I'll go.
Now, standby
Cue!
- [Limit] Hitch!
- [Symbol] Don't do it, don't do it, hey
- [Sound of door opening]
- [Symbol] No, what, not yet?
[Limit] No, it’s all over
To check one more time
Mingeun said he found his eyes.
- [Symbol] Really? where?
- [♪ Calm music]
They say Grandpa Yoon Nam-gi had it.
[Symbol] In that video at that time
What are you holding in your hand?
Wow
In my past life with Mingeun
It must have been a great connection, huh?
[Hando’s crackling sound]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
- [Limit] Good luck
- [Symbol] Yes
[Sound of intake of breath]
[Shows cutely] Ah, now
I need to edit it, yuyu
Later at dawn, our kiss princess
I'll go see your face for a moment
Heart byung
[page]
Okay, let’s finish this quickly and let’s go.
[Sympathy of symbol] Let's cheer!
[Sound of strength]
- [Keyboard operation sound]
- [Limit in video] What is a video clip?
- [Sound of Han Han’s words in the video]
- [Siho smiles] Young Go Jjal
Ah, this idiot is really, huh?
- [Creaking sound]
- [♪ Meaningful music]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Tense sound effect]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[♪ Meaningful music flows]
- [Substitute] Oh, did you add subtitles?
- [Keyboard operation sound]
[Soryong] How do you feel?
[Daeyong] It looks like a movie
[Soryong] This is the opening
Whose idea was this?
[Symbol] Ah…
[Daeyong’s Elasticity]
[Daeyong] I’m from the drama department.
What's different?
[Soryong] If you just remove the cruel parts,
It'll be okay, right?
- [Daeyong] Yes
- [Symbol] This is a doll
- [So Ryong] I know
- [Symbol] Ah
[Daeyong] Hey, you guys are surprisingly good together.
- [clacking sound]
- [Symbol] Yes, sum
Huh?
Well, isn’t Captain Bae’s acting good?
[So-ryong] Captain Bae, stop using it.
- [♪ Heavy and interesting music]
- [Camera operating sound]
[So Long] When thick darkness falls on the city
An old man who reveals himself
The online community started a few months ago.
spread out to the center
creepy urban legends
Our reporters
What we met at the end of the rumor
Of a genius boy who grew up into a monster
- terrible
- [Shoot rain sound]
It was bare-faced.
- [Emphasized sound effect]
- [Sharp ringing sound]
[Sound of hitting]
- [Blender operating sound]
- Even the moment of death
To protect Mingeun’s eyes
Old man Mr. Yoon with charred hands
This video we obtained is
Old man Yoon is the main culprit.
Contrary to Son’s claim,
We were talking about something completely different
[sudden sound]
[Junyoung] It’s just a matter of touch anyway
I won't go to jail
My goal is to kill 100 people.
Ha, her eyes were really pretty.
[Soyong on TV] The value of life
To the monster boy who laughed at me
Animal life and human life
Just a toy for show off
It hasn't passed
mocking the value of life by relying on the law
- To this monster boy
- [Junyoung’s trembling breathing]
- Are there any more indulgences?
- [♪ Heavy music on TV]
- Does it exist?
- [Angrily breathing]
held in the hands of the weak
trigger of the final truth
It was Trigger Oh So-ryong.
[Junyoung] Oh my, fuck!
- [Rough breathing]
- [Junyoung’s mother] Junyoung
Junyoung, Junyoung, Junyoung
What should I do?
[Junyoung’s mock urgent breathing]
[Detective Yoo] Arrested.
[Junyoung] Don’t come
- [Junyoung’s mother] Oh, no.
- [Junyoung] Don’t come!
- [Detective 1] Come out, come out.
- [Junyoung’s swearing sound]
- [Detective 1] Stay still, stay still
[Junyoung’s mother] No!
[Junyoung] Hey, you bastards!
- [Detective 2] Stay still!
- [Junyoung] Let go of this!
- [Detective 2] Hey, put the handcuffs on, quickly!
- [Junyoung’s screaming sound]
[yawn]
[Detective] Go
[Junyoung’s mother] Hey, you guys!
[Detective Yu] Uh-huh, why are you like this, uh-huh!
[clattering sound]
Ah, why are you like this?
You trampled on my son's life
Do you think you can live well?
I thought you'd appreciate it
What?
- Edward Camper
- [♪ Dark Music]
Famous serial killer with IQ 145
[Soryong] I have loved animals since I was young.
I played with cruel torture.
When I was a teenager
for the first time
I murdered my grandmother and grandfather.
Less than 10 years later
The final murder target
It was my real mother.
Killed him by hitting his head with a hammer
cut off the head
They said it was made from a dart board.
Sigh
What I saved you before
Luckily you know
[shaking breathing]
[Tense sound effect]
On behalf of my mother
First, to the dead victims.
at least
You have to pretend to be sorry.
At least I'm an adult
I'm that child's mother.
dead second child
Because I am also a mother
[Crying breathing]
[Detective Yu] Now, let’s go, okay?
go
That
Can't I get in the car behind you?
- [Junyoung’s mother] Huh?
- [Radio radio operating sound]
[Detective Yoo] Go to the car behind, hey, go.
[Oncoming car engine sound]
[Lawyer] Mother, mother!
[Heavy breathing]
This is a resignation letter
You lied to me, right?
The reason I have a backsliding is
Just because I hate it, yeah
yes
- [Sound of car door opening and closing]
- [Detective Yu’s encouraging voice]
[Car engine sound receding]
[♪ Music with a sense of tension]
[Laughs]
[Tak]
[Symbol] Hey, the police are accompanying you to the interview.
Allowing this is
Ah, our team leader
It's really cool, right?
- [Limit] Yes
- [Symbol] Yes?
[Limit] Yes?
Did you just say 'yes'?
[Daeyong] Get off work
It's my first work, so why not have a beer?
[Kiho sighs] Oh my
Because I'm watching it again now
I have to fix everything.
[Daeyong] I can’t watch it again
Son Jun-young's rich father
Searching like crazy
I count every minute and second
- If you're wrong, I'll sue you.
- [Sigh]
You shouldn't give any distance at all
[Kiho] Then this is the first broadcast.
Is this the last room?
What's next
Broadcasting is going to be boring, so what?
Even though my name is Ibbong, please give me a Dharma Kara.
[Sound of lid closing]
Come to work, man.
[Daeyong clears his throat]
[Symbol] Wow, Mr.!
Wow, Mr.!
Wow, this is that once a year thing
Our CP asks Beopka whether he should see it or not.
- Seed method
- [Daeyong] What, man?
[Symbol] It’s an honor, Mr.
- Can we eat cow, CP?
- [Daeyong] Hey
How pretty are the cow's eyes?
Eat pork belly, pork belly
[Writer Hong] Aren’t pigs cute?
[Daeyong] Hey, over there
[Symbol] Author
I'm calling you
[Writer Hong] Me?
that cabinet key
Give me one of mine too
Materials you need
If you tell me, I...
[Daeyong] What am I?
Do I have to get permission for each one?
If you don't have a spare
Please make a copy and give me one
Good job
- [Small symbol] Brother, brother
- [Clicking door sound]
They said the cow didn't like it because it had pretty eyes.
How about the lamb restaurant in front of you?
- [Limit] I have a prior contract.
- [Symbol] Yes?
I'll go
limit brother
Does the appointment take a long time?
brother
that human
Didn't you hear that rumor somewhere?
[Limit] How much is it all together?
[Staff] Mortuary costs for shrouds
Even body storage fees
A total of 2.78 million won.
200!
78…
[Card terminal operation sound]
Hey, interest-free...
As long as possible...
yes
[Woman] Oh, are you here?
[Sound of people talking]
[Skipping sound]
- [Man 1] Are you okay?
- [Man 2] Hey, be careful.
[Man 3] Hey, uncle.
Would you mind?
[Man 2] Oh, yeah
Thank you, Ayu
[Woman] You need to be careful
[Man 4] Yes
There have been a lot of hardships during this time.
Come on in and rest.
- Take a break, uh, take a break.
- [Sound of people greeting]
[♪ Lonely and soft music
OV, Meego 'Someday']
[light sigh]
[Student] Hey…
Here he is, the grandfather who appeared on TV.
Is this a mortuary?
Uh, yes
It's true that Yoon Nam-ki's grandfather is buried.
While watching our broadcast and searching
I came to see you
May I say hello?
Uh, sure
[♪ Soft music continues]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Man] Greetings, greetings
Please come in
[cell phone vibrating sound]
- Just a moment.
- [Hairdresser] Oh, yes
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Sound of intake of breath]
[sigh]
[Hairdresser] Hair
What can I do for you?
I want to change it
in a different style
[Sound of cutting]
[clunking sound]
[rattling sound]
[urgent breathing]
[Sound effect heightening tension]
[surprised gasp]
- [Sound of difficulty]
- [♪ Tension-tinged music]
[Sound of strength]
[Dr. Trigger] ‘Jesus
He said to Thomas
[Switch operation sound]
''He who believes without seeing
I'm happy''
[Feeding away]
Now your faith
Shall we test it?
[Mobile phone power sound]
- [Mobile phone vibrating sound]
- [popping sound]
It's real this time
[Thumping sound effect]
[♪ Lonely and soft music
OV, Meego 'Someday']